PARESH HADIYAL **UI/UX DESIGNER**

PROFILE

My self Paresh Hadiyal basically from Mumbai, India. I have successfully completed Graphic designing form walkin institute and UI UX designing from internshala and i am currently working as Freelancer as graphic designer since 2 years. I have expertise in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Adobe Indesign, Corel Draw, Figma

CONTACT



Address:

Bhiwandi-421302 District Thane. Maharashtra



Phones:

+91 9762910916 +91 9313614209



pareshhadiyal007@gmail.com

SKILLS

- + Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Coreldraw
- InDesign
- + Adobe XD
- + Figma

LANGUAGES

- + Hindi
- + English
- + Marathi
- + Gujarati

WORK EXPERIENCE

D-Badami

(December 2019 -November 2020)

Textile Designer:-Create and Developed New Design, Textile Designer, Print Design, Mock Up Design for Textile.

Studio

(2017-2018)

Studio Designer:- Album Designer, Photoshop editing, Video Editing, Photography, Video Shooting.

EDUCATION

University Of Mumbai

(2015 - 2018)

Bachelor of Science in Information and Technology (Bsc IT)

Walkin institute

(2019 - 2020)

Graphic Designer

My course include design software like Adobe photoshop, Adobe illustrator, Adobe indesign, Corel Draw.

Internshala training

(2021 - 2021)

Ui/Ux Designer

The training consisted of Design Basics, Design with Figma, Creating your Design System, Design a Finance App of your own, Convert your Figma design into a native iOS & Android App and What to do Next

AWARDS

INTERNSHALA

INTERNSHALA TRANING CERTIFICATE UI/UX DESIGNER 2021

WALKIN INSTITUTE

DESIGN CERTIFICATE GRAPHIC DESIGNER 2019



2/14/2021 Behance :: Work Experience

Paresh Hadiyal

Ui/Ux Designer, Graphic Designer

Mumbai, India

9762910916 pareshhadiyal007@gmail.com be.net/pareshhadiyal

My self Paresh Hadiyal basically from Mumbai, India. I have successfully completed Graphic designing and UI UX designing from internshala and i am currently working as Freelancer as graphic designer since 2 years. I have expertise in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Adobe Indesign, Corel Draw, Figma

To make use of my interpersonal skills to achieve goals of a company that focuses on customer satisfaction and customer experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

D-Badami

Head Designer (Textile Designer)

Create and Developed New Design, Textile Designer, Print Design, Mock Up Design for Textile.

December 2019 - November 2020 | India

Studio

Studio Designer

Album Designer, Photoshop editing, Video Editing, Photography, Video Shooting.

March 2017 - February 2018 | India

EDUCATION

University Of Mumbai

Bachelor of Science in Information and Technology (Bsc IT)

June 2015 - April 2018 | India

Internshala Training

Ui/Ux Designer

The training consisted of Design Basics, Design with Figma, Creating your Design System, Design a Finance App of your own, Convert your Figma design into a native iOS & Android App and What to do Next modules.

January 2021 - February 2021 | India

Walkin Institute

Graphic Designer

My course include design software like Adobe photoshop, Adobe illustrator, Adobe indesign,Corel Draw.

May 2019 - November 2019 | India

LANGUAGES

English (Conversational)

Hindi (Fluent)

Gujarati (Native)

Marathi (Conversational)

AWARDS

Internshala

Internshala Traning Certificate

2021

Walkin Institute

Graphic Design Certificate

2019

SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Indesign, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, Art, CorelDraw, Creativity, Figma, Graphic Design, UI/UX Design

TRANING

UI/UX Design Internshala Trainings, Online Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

Successfully completed a six weeks online certied training on UI/UX Design. The training consisted of Design Basics, Design with Figma, Creating your Design System, Design a Finance App of your own, Convert your Figma design into a native iOS & Android App and What to do Next modules. In the nal assessment, I scored 71% marks.